plr365.com 2019-05-21

# PLR365.com | Privacy Policy

**What Information Do We Collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To process your transaction and provide updates pertaining to your order.  
• To provide customer support and help answer your enquiries.  
• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.  
• To send periodic emails. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  
• To improve our website. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

We only keep your information as long as we need to, for the purposes listed above. When we don’t need it any more we delete it securely. Please note if you ask us to stop using your information for marketing purposes, we may need to retain some of your data to ensure your details are kept on our “Do Not Mail” lists. If you’d like to know more about what information we hold on you or have any enquiries about the security or our processing of your information, please do contact us in writing by email.

**Do We Disclose Any Information to Third Parties?**

We may share your information in the following circumstances:

• To prevent, investigate, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service or as otherwise required by law.  
• Personal data may also be shared with a company that acquires our business, whether through acquisition, merger, dissolution, bankruptcy, reorganization, or other similar proceedings. If this happens, we will notify you by email.  
• Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Except as listed above, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personal data to third parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep your information confidential.

**How We Protect Your Information**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

**Third Party Links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.plr365.com/terms/

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on 25/05/2018
